This tiny little transformer was built
for the moon. It's only about the size
of a baseball, but inside are cameras,
two wheels, and a tail for stability.
Its little size is great for small
spacecraft, but also for getting into
tiny vents and craters on the lunar
surface where larger rovers can't go. It
has three modes of transportation to
navigate the rough lunar surface. It's
got butterfly, crawl, and turning
around. Two of these little guys
launched on this Japanese rocket in
2024, and scientists just published
these photos that they took on the lunar
surface. So to see what the robot
transformers send back next, subscribe.